Novi Sad, Serbia

Summary

Throughout my career, I continuously think about growth and innovation. I am committed to empowering others to achieve their goals and believe in collective progress. I am open to new knowledge and experiences, and I work every day to improve myself as a person and as a programmer. I believe that continuous learning is key to success and I readily embrace challenges to reach my full potential.

Work Experience

Neotech Solutions - Software Engineer

Belgrade - May 2023 - Jan 2024

- Development of new functionalities for the gambling app: Enhanced user experience and boosted revenue through active feature development.
- Debugging and optimizing Node.js microservices (Express.js, NestJS): Improved app stability and performance, reducing response time.
- Writing End-to-end and Unit tests: Decreased errors, enhanced code quality, and accelerated feature development.

Forwardslash - Software Engineer

Novi Sad - Apr 2021 - May 2023

- Developing an e-commerce app in PHP and Vue.js with a Headless approach: Created a scalable platform allowing flexible UI customization and enhanced content management.
- Working on Node.js (NestJS) backend for an apartment rental app using AWS: Built a reliable, scalable architecture for efficient data management and high app availability.
- Implementing new features in WordPress apps: Enhanced user experience and platform capabilities, driving increased user engagement and client satisfaction.
- Creating demo apps in Flutter: Explored mobile development possibilities, expanding skills and tech understanding.

Forwardslash - Software Engineer Internship

Novi Sad - Feb 2021 - Mar 2021

- Application of knowledge acquired at the university regarding Web development and OOP.
- Acquiring new knowledge about PHP and Vue.js.

Education

Higher Education Technical School of Professional Studies in Novi Sad – VTSNS

Master of Engineering - MEng, Information Technology

2021 - 2023

Topic of thesis: Creating android applications for children with autism in Flutter.

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Information Technology

2018 - 2021

Topic of thesis: WordPress theme and plugin development.

Certificate

SmartInIT - Web Programming

2020

- Introduction to HTML, CSS, JavaScript and C#.
- Backend application development in C# and ASP.NET.

Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, PHP, Dart
- Frameworks: NestJS, WordPress, Vue.js, React.js
- Cloud Technologies : AWS, Firebase
- Databases : MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL